tamron.com 2010-10-20

# DSLR and other Digital Camera Lenses FAQs, Tamron USA

**Privacy Policy Statement**

This is the web site of **TAMRON USA, INC.**

Our postal address is **10 AUSTIN BLVD., COMMACK, NY 11725**

We can be reached via e-mail at [webmaster@tamron.com](mailto:webmaster@tamron.com) or you can reach us by telephone at 631-858-8400. 

**To Whom This Statement Applies**  
This Statement only applies to Tamron USA, Inc. This Statement does not apply to affiliated entities of Tamron USA, Inc. or to third parties.

**The Information We Collect**  
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes no information regarding the domain or e-mail address. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail; the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our share your photos area; and information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information, newsletter registration, new product registration and event registration.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page and to contact consumers that have requested such about new product information, special offers and more. The information we collect is never shared with other organizations for marketing or commercial purposes.

**How We Use the Information We Collect**  
We use your Personal Information to respond to and fulfill your requests for Tamron USA, Inc.'s products and services and to market our products and services, including:

  * to send you our catalogs and other offers through mail. If you supply us with your postal address on-line you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please let us know by calling us at the number provided above. Please provide us with your exact name and address. We will be sure your name is removed from the list;

  * to send you our email newsletters and information about contests, sweepstakes, specials offers and other information if you have opted to receive them. To stop emails about special offers, access the Un-subscribe link provided in the email message, by e-mailing us at webmaster@tamron.com, or by calling us at the number provided above. Please provide us with your exact name and email address. We will be sure your email address is removed from the list. It will not affect your chances of winning if you choose to opt-out of receiving such offers at any time after having chosen to participate in one;

  * to contact you about the status of or to obtain additional information about the event you have signed up for, or about any issue regarding your photo contest submission or product registration. Persons who supply us with their telephone numbers, email or mail address on-line may receive telephone, mail or email contact from us with information regarding contests, product registration or event registration. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, mail or email, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address, or by calling us at the above telephone number. Please provide us with your name and contact information. We will be sure your name is removed from the list.

We ask for only the Personal Information necessary to administer any of the items listed above.

**Our Use of Cookies**  
With respect to cookies, we use technology to collect anonymous, non-Personal Information that indicates how our site is used by visitors. We use this information to improve our site, for example by enhancing pages or features that are visited frequently, and on occasion we may share this information with our affiliates or other third party companies to help us plan for technical improvements. This information will not identify you or any other user of our web site as an individual. We use cookies to understand how our site visitors link to our site and what pages they view during their visit.

If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address.

**With Respect To Security**  
We always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our site.

**Updates to this Statement**  
From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically, we will use for these new purposes only data collected from the time of the policy change forward.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above addresses or phone number.
